{
  "data": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "What is the name of the Griffin family dog?",
      "answers": ["Brian", "Stewie", "Meg", "Chris"],
      "correct_answer": "Brian"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "What is the name of Lois Griffin's father?",
      "answers": [
        "Carter Pewterschmidt",
        "Peter Griffin",
        "Glenn Quagmire",
        "Cleveland Brown"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Carter Pewterschmidt"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "What is the name of the town where the Griffin family lives?",
      "answers": ["Quahog", "Springfield", "Simpsons", "Griffinville"],
      "correct_answer": "Quahog"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "What is the name of the bar where Peter, Joe, Quagmire, and Cleveland go to?",
      "answers": [
        "The Drunken Clam",
        "The Griffin Tavern",
        "The Quahog Pub",
        "The Pawtucket Patriot Ale House"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "The Drunken Clam"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "What is the name of Stewie Griffin's teddy bear?",
      "answers": ["Rupert", "Winston", "Barney", "Wally"],
      "correct_answer": "Rupert"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "What is the name of the chicken who is Peter Griffin's nemesis?",
      "answers": [
        "Lois Griffin",
        "Meg Griffin",
        "Stewie Griffin",
        "Ernie The Giant Chicken"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Ernie The Giant Chicken"
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "What is the name of the news anchor on Channel 5?",
      "answers": [
        "Tom Tucker",
        "Diane Simmons",
        "Peter Griffin",
        "Stewie Griffin"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Tom Tucker"
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "What is the name of the police officer who is Joe Swanson's partner?",
      "answers": [
        "Brian Griffin",
        "Stewie Griffin",
        "Glenn Quagmire",
        "Akira Yoshida"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Akira Yoshida"
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "What is the name of the mall that the Griffin family frequently goes to?",
      "answers": [
        "The Quahog Mall",
        "The Springfield Mall",
        "The Simpsons Mall",
        "The Griffin Mall"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "The Quahog Mall"
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "Who does Stewie want to kill?",
      "answers": ["Meg", "Chris", "Peter", "Lois"],
      "correct_answer": "Lois"
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "Where was Peter born?",
      "answers": ["Mexico", "Canada", "United States", "Russia"],
      "correct_answer": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "Which Family Guy character is obsessed with world domination?",
      "answers": ["Meg", "Chris", "Stewie", "Brian"],
      "correct_answer": ""
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "Who is the mayor of Quahog?",
      "answers": ["Bill Bixby", "Adam West", "Lynda Carter", "Burt Ward"],
      "correct_answer": "Adam West"
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "Who founded the city of Quahog?",
      "answers": [
        "Griffin Peterson",
        "Adam West",
        "Miles Musket",
        "A Magical Talking Calm"
      ],
      "correct_answer": "Griffin Peterson"
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "What did Peter change Meg's name to on her birth certificate?",
      "answers": ["Megillah", "Megatron", "Megolavina", "Mega Millions"],
      "correct_answer": "Megatron"
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "Who burned The Drunken Clam to the ground?",
      "answers": ["Peter", "Brian", "God", "Stewie"],
      "correct_answer": "Peter"
    }
  ]
}
